nowfoods.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy | NOW Foods

This Privacy Policy explains the privacy practices of NOW Health Group, Inc. (“NHGI”), and describes the way we use and protect the information we collect from our website nowfoods.com and other NHGI sites linked to this website) (collectively referred to as the “Site”) about customers and users.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

  * We collect information that you provide when logging in to your account, entering contests, sweepstakes or promotions, placing an order, subscribing to any newsletters, responding to surveys, utilizing our store locator services or other requests for information.
  * Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.
  * Information received in connection with providing your service or fulfilling your purchase order.
  * Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To process transactions.
  * To respond to your request or other correspondence.
  * To send you emails containing information and updates pertaining to your order or request, notifying you of any product recall in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, or related product or service information, etc. if such information was requested.
  * To administer and fulfill a marketing promotion, contest, sweepstake, survey or other site feature.
  * We may share information with trusted third party companies, entities and individuals to perform functions on our behalf (i.e., credit card processing companies, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional distribution); provided, however, that these third parties may access your personal information only on a confidential basis and only to the extent necessary to perform their functions, and all third party vendors must abide by our privacy policy.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.
  * These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information or SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely.
  * While we have excellent security measures in place that meet or exceed industry standards, no data transmission over the Internet is one hundred percent secure. Although our top priority is to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you submit to our Site.

## DO WE USE COOKIES?

NHGI collects information, and we authorize our trusted third party vendors to collect information, about users over time across our Site and for other services. To do this, we and/or our third party vendors use several common tracking tools. These may include Cookies, Web Beacons, Flash Cookies, and similar technologies.

We may use these cookies and tracking technologies to: recognize new or past customers and to store your password if you are registered to our Site and to improve our Site; serve you with interest-based or targeted advertising; observe your behaviors and browsing activities over time across multiple websites or other platforms; better understand the interests of our customers and our Site visitors; and in connection with an email delivery and marketing company to send emails that you have agreed to receive.  Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email messages and at our Site to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how our visitors use our Site.

You can stop certain types of cookies from being downloaded on your computer by selecting the appropriate settings on your web browser. Web browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new browser cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new browser cookie and how to disable existing cookies. You can find out how to do this for your specific browser by visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). In addition, your mobile device settings may allow you to prohibit mobile app platforms (such as Apple and Google) from sharing certain information obtained by automated means with app developers and operators such as us. Our Services are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers. Please note that without cookies or other automated tools we use to collect this type of data, you may not be able to use all the features of our Services.

## DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information without your consent. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. We may use this information to address network integrity and security issues or to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities or violations of our other policies.

We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  1. conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NHGI;
  2. protect and defend the rights or property of the NHGI network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the NHGI network of sites and related properties;
  3. identify persons who may be violating the law, the NHGI legal notice and Website User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the NOW Health Group, Inc. Network or its related properties; and
  4. cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

## ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This Online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Site and not to information collected offline.

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Some content or applications on the Site are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third party websites may use cookies alone or in conjunction with Web Beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services and these third party sites may have privacy practices different than ours. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.  Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Each third party website is solely responsible for its own privacy practices and use of the personally identifiable information it collects from you.  NHGI does not endorse any third party website or its privacy practices.  Links to privacy policies of a few third party websites that are featured on our Site are listed below.  
<https://privacy.google.com/>  
<https://www.viralsweep.com/privacy>  
<https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>  
<https://www.addtoany.com/privacy>  
<https://destini.co/privacy-policy/>

## CHILDREN UNDER 18

This Site is not directed to nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, you may only use this Site with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

## YOUR CONSENT

By using our Site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## HOW TO CONTACT US AND OPT OUT

If you have any questions or concerns about our online policy for this Site or its implementation, or you want to opt out of any subscriptions, you may follow the link at the bottom of an email correspondence or contact us at 244 Knollwood Dr., Bloomingdale, IL 60108 or Telephone: 888-669-3663.  Specific privacy and data retention requests can be made to the Webmaster using the form available at: <https://www.nowfoods.com/now/about-now/contact-us>.

You can find more information about the United States DAA opt out program here:  
<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or the NAI opt out program hers:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

You can find more information about the European Union (EU)/European Economic Area (EEA) EDAA opt out program here: <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

## TERRITORIAL USE RESTRICTIONS AND JURISDICTION

These web pages are controlled and operated by NOW Health Group, Inc. in the United States. NHGI makes no representation that this Privacy Policy complies with any applicable laws outside the United States. Those who choose to access these pages from locations outside the United States do so at their own initiative and risk.

This Privacy Policy and other policies on this Site shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois. All claims, disputes, and lawsuits arising out of or in connection with this Privacy Policy shall be resolved or adjudicated in DuPage County, Illinois.
